JORGE SARRICOLEA

WEB DEVELOPER AND UX/UI DESIGNER



ABOUT ME



I am a Web Developer specialized in UI/UX Design, with 2 years of experience working on different projects. I am a Personal Finance and Technology enthusiast, always keeping up with the latest trends, and have the ability to learn anything I set my mind to.

Check my own web page!

jorgesarricolea.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

Co-Leader at En-Coders Programming Club | February 2023 - Present

AAAI Student Chapter México

I teach programming algorithms in Java and Python, how to use Git and GitHub and operating systems to students on my university. (Non-profit).

Personal Portfolio | January 2023 - Present

GitHub: Portfolio-2.0

I am developing the second version of my portfolio, with an improvement in UI and UX, adding more projects that I have developed with JavaScript, HTML and CSS. **Go to my GitHub to check out all my projects**.

Web Developer in Datamatic Software | June 2022 - July 2022

LinkedIn: Datamatic Software

I worked on the Front-End of an employee registration and management page for a United States company. Adding new features and connecting Air Table API.

Full responsive web app marketplace on Bubble.io | January 2018 - Present

jumwork.com

I designed the whole brand and user interface from scratch on Bubble. Integration with Stripe API and others in Back-End process. Work with differents plugins, like Sendgrid. I upgraded old pages to the new responsive engine.

EDUCATION

Instituto Tecnológico de Mérida

Ingeniería en Sistemas Computacionales. 2020 - 2024

Platzi

Interface Design Course. 2020 HTML and CSS Practical Course. 2021 Software Engineering Fundamentals. 2021 Frontend Developer Course. 2022

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, JQuery, Node.js, Jest (Testing), Bubble.io, Java, Python, Git, Github, VSCode, Boostrap, Trello, Notion, Slack, Miro, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Premiere Pro, Figma